export default [
    {
        question: "who",
        answer: "qui"
    },
    {
        question: "with who",
        answer: "avec qui",
        highlight: "I talks",
    },
    {
        question: "for who",
        answer: "pour qui",
        highlight: "You talks",
    },
    {
        question: "from who",
        answer: "de qui",
        highlight: "She talks",
    },
    {
        question: "what",
        answer: "quoi",
        highlight: "You talks",
    },
    {
        question: "what (qu'est ce que)",
        answer: "qu'est ce que",
        highlight: "You talks",
    },
    {
        question: "what (que)",
        answer: "que",
        highlight: "You talks",
    },
    {
        question: "Where",
        answer: "o√π",
        highlight: "You talks",
    },
    {
        question: "when",
        answer: "quand",
        highlight: "You talks",
    },
    {
        question: "how",
        answer: "comment",
        highlight: "You talks",
    },
    {
        question: "how much",
        answer: "combien",
        highlight: "You talks",
    },
    {
        question: "how many",
        answer: "combien de",
        highlight: "You talks",
    },
    {
        question: "which (m)",
        answer: "quel",
        highlight: "You talks",
    },
    {
        question: "which (f)",
        answer: "quelle",
        highlight: "You talks",
    },
    {
        question: "which (m-pl)",
        answer: "quels",
        highlight: "You talks",
    },
    {
        question: "which one (m)",
        answer: "lequel",
        highlight: "You talks",
    },
    {
        question: "which one (f)",
        answer: "laquelle",
        highlight: "You talks",
    },
    {
        question: "which one (m-pl)",
        answer: "lesquels",
        highlight: "You talks",
    },
    {
        question: "which one (f-pl)",
        answer: "lesquelles",
        highlight: "You talks",
    },
]